Acacia Imler

1400 North Park Blvd Apt 801 Grapevine, TX 76051

acaciaraquelrn@gmail.com

214-542-8088

Summary

Empathetic, hard-working critical care nurse with two years of experience in a long-term acute care setting looking forward to exploring a new field. Collaborative team player eager to provide emotional support to emergency room and critical care patients. Ambitious and teachable while also being efficient in a critical emergency.

Employment History

Kindred Hospital ICU, Dallas, TX December 2015- November 2017 **ICU** Conemaugh Hospital, Johnstown, PA May 2015-November 2015 Surgical Trauma patient load of seven to eight patients White House/Black Market Sales, Southlake, TX October 2011-February 2015 Sales, top UPT in international company Bailey's Prime, Dallas and Cedar Hill, TX July 2008-November 2011 Event planner

Education_

University of Texas at Arlington

BSN, nine remaining classes

North Lake College, Irving, TX

- Phi Theta Kappa, 3.6 GPA
- Delivered graduation speech "Overcoming Obstacles"

Professional Skills

- **BLS/ACLS**
- Daily Blood Draws
- Rapid response/code team
- Management of critically complex patients including drips (Levophed, Insulin, Propofol, Morphine, etc)

Enrolled

Graduated December 2014

- LVAD trained in heartmate I, II, and III
- Hospice Patients and families
- Vent weaning
- Wound care including wound vac treatment

References_

Deborah Mosley, UTSW	512-995-1969
Davis Holt, MSN at Baylor PCU, co-worker	214-202-0926
Maria McClung, Kindred Administration, co-worker.	